你们好啊  亲爱的
Hello, my darlings!
大家今天都好吗
How is everyone today?
声音都好好的吧
In good voice, I trust.
谢谢
Thank you.
贝拉  亲爱的  你知道我觉得我们该怎么办吗
Bella, darling, you know what I think we should do?
我觉得我们该简化一下
I think we should simplify it.
让主持人进来  介绍我
Let the hosts come in, introduce me,
我们谈谈慈善项目的事
we'll pitch the charity a little bit,
百老汇心连心  然后...
broadway hearts for hearts, and, um...
记住  她唱到第一个
And remember... when she gets to the first
"我们为爱所做之事"  准备进行降雪
"The Things We Do For Love," stand by for snow drop.
开始吧
Shall we?
这首歌一直是我最喜欢的一首
This number has always been one of my favorites...
经典的老情歌
A classic love song from back in the day.
准备  等信号
Stand by for cue.
沟通是问题的答案
Communication is the problem to the answer.
你有他的号码  手也握着电话
You've got his number, and your hand is on the phone.
天气突变  线路不通
The weather's turned, and all the lines are down.
我们为爱所做之事啊
The things we do for love.
降雪  降雪
Cue snow. Cue snow.
*就如走在雨中雪里*
*Like walking in the rain and the snow*
快下雪
Get the snow going.
*无处可去*
*And there's nowhere to go*
*感觉自己好像在憔悴*
*And you're feeling like a part of you is dying*
*你想在他眼中得到答案*
*And you're looking for the answer in his eyes*
这程度不行
Need more snow than that.
*你以为你们要分手*
*You think you're gonna break up*
*他却说想跟你和好*
*Then he says he wants to make up*
天呐
Oh, my god!
贝克特警监  你午餐会议的
So, Captain Beckett, have you successfully completed
目的达到了吗
your agenda for your lunch meeting?
是的  三次呢
Indeed I did... three times.
三次
Three?
史上最棒的会议
Best meeting ever.
谁能想到
Who would have thought
秘密约会能这么有成效
that secret dating would be so productive?
是啊  我们公开的争吵
I know. Our public fights have made
让我们私下的会面更加
our private time so much more...
激烈了
Intense.
-是吧  -是啊
- Right? - Yes.
警监还有空再议一题吗
I don't suppose the captain has time for one more agenda?
抱歉  我也想
Oh, I'm sorry. I wish I could.
但我得去总部跟盖茨警监会面
But I have to make this meeting with Captain Gates at 1pp.
那盖茨其实是指代维克拉姆
And is "Gates" code for "Vikram"
而总部其实是指你们的脱衣舞吧藏身处吗
and "1pp" your secret strip-club hideout?
不  跟盖茨的会面绝对是真的
No. The meeting with Gates is very real.
听我说  里克  我不会再私自行动了
Look, Rick, - I'm done playing lone wolf,
我保证  等时机成熟
and I promise you... when the time is right,
我会把洛克塞特的一切都告诉你
I will loop you in on everything LokSat.
我理解这是一个秘密行动
I-I mean, I get that the whole thing is a covert op.
我只是想说  我可以作为你扳倒洛克塞特的
I'm just saying... I could be your secret weapon
秘密武器
in taking LokSat down.
相信我  邦德  等时机到了
Trust me, 007... when it's time,
我们要一起扳倒洛克塞特
you and I will take down LokSat together.
在此期间  我会通过隔壁
Meanwhile, - I will be sneaking in and out
溜进溜出
of the building next door to get here.
那我呢
While I do what?
提供支持和安慰
Provide support and comfort.
很多很多的安慰
Lots and lots of comfort.
再见
Bye.
妈妈  你今天过得如何
Mother. How's your day going?
妈妈
Mother!
理查德  亲爱的
Richard, darling.
谢天谢地  你来了
Thank god you're here.
我尽快赶过来的
I came as soon as I could.
-你没事吧  -没事  别担心我
- Are you all right? - Yeah. Don't worry about me.
我们该考虑的是可怜的好姑娘罗宾
It's poor, sweet Robyn that we should be thinking about.
-你认识她  -我们昨天才认识
- You knew her? - I just met her yesterday.
她观看了整个彩排
She... she sat through an entire rehearsal,
还一直等着
and then she waited around
跟我说谢谢
so she could come up and thank me.
她真是
She was just...
她真的很可爱
She was lovely.
亲爱的  你要保证
Darling, I want you to promise me
你会亲自处理这件案子
that you will handle this case personally
查清真凶
and find out who did this.
当然
Yeah, of course. Of course.
奶奶  我带你回家吧
Gram, why don't I take you home?
好
Okay.
太好了  谢谢  好
Perfect. Thank you. Okay.
玛莎还好吗
How's Martha?
吓得不轻
Uh, shaken up.
怎么回事
What happened?
被害人罗宾·金  20岁
Victim is Robyn King, 20 years old.
是剧院的夜班守卫
Works as the theater's night janitor.
从尸斑和尸温判断  死亡时间
Based on lividity and body temp, I estimate the time of death
约为昨晚9点到11点之间
is last night between 9:00 and 11:00.
死因  钝器击伤致死
Cause of death... blunt-force trauma.
凶手击中了罗宾的头  然后把她塞进雪箱
Killer hit Robyn in the head, stuffed her in the snow box,
升到了房梁上
and lifted her up to the rafter.
她在那儿流血致死
Where she bled out.
这是克里斯·杰克逊
This is Chris Jackson.
他是剧院制作经理
He's the theater's production manager.
理查德·卡塞尔  是你雇佣了罗宾
Richard Castle. So, you're the one who hired Robyn?
是的  我起初还有点紧张
Yes. And I was a little nervous at first.
罗宾是释放犯
Robyn was an ex-con,
但她的假释官敦促我给她份工作
but her parole officer pressed me to give her a job...
还保证说她非常值得信任
Promised that she was completely trustworthy.
昨晚之前从未出过问题
And until last night, there hadn't been a single problem.
昨晚怎么了
What happened last night?
有个女人来找罗宾
A woman showed up looking for Robyn,
她非常愤怒
and she was pissed.
罗宾认识她吗
And Robyn knew her?
是的  她喊她"妈妈"
Oh, yeah. She called her "mama."
但她们显然不是幸福的一家人
But they clearly weren't a happy family.
我离开时还听到罗宾威胁说
As I was leaving, I heard Robyn threaten to call the cops
如果她妈再靠近她  她就叫警察
if her mom ever came near her again.
我真不该就那么走掉
I shouldn't have left them alone.
如果我当时没走  罗宾或许不会死
Robyn might still be alive if I had just...stayed behind.
意外情况
So, here's a surprise.
根据罗宾的记录显示  她妈妈在她五岁时就死了
Robyn's records show that her mother died when she was 5.
-那这个"妈妈"是谁  -问得好
- Then who's "mama"? - Exactly.
我还发现了一个谜团
And here's another mystery that I found...
据罗宾的地铁卡显示
according to Robyn's MetroCard,
她出狱之后每周两晚都会
she's been taking subway trips up to Spanish Harlem
坐地铁去西班牙哈莱姆区
two nights a week ever since she was released from prison.
每次都是11:30左右离开
Each time, she leaves around 11:30 p.m.,
待近两小时才回家
stays for almost two hours before going home.
能从财务方面看出她是去做什么了吗
Any indication in her financials what she's doing up there?
还没查到什么
No, nothing yet.
-我得接一下  -好
- I got to take that. - Okay.
我听说玛莎的事了
So, I heard about Martha.
你怎么没打断会议  叫我出来啊
Why didn't you pull me out of the meeting?
是这样  我想过的
You know what? I thought about it.
但因为我们的地下关系什么的
But this whole new... secret relationship...
我不知道有什么规矩
I wasn't quite sure what the rules were.
她没事吧
Well, i-is she okay?
身体上是没事
Physically, yes. She's fine.
但情绪不太好
Emotionally, not so much.
她要我答应她一定亲自揪出杀了罗宾的凶手
She made me promise to help track down Robyn's killer.
当然  但你得知道我在明面上
Of course, - but you know that publicly,
得做出反对
I can't agree to that.
什么意思
What do you mean?
意思是  我爱你
Well, it means that I love you,
但现在  我得吼你了
but right now, - I'm gonna have to yell at you.
卡塞尔
Castle!
我们说过的  你不能来这儿
We talked about this! You can't be here!
抱歉了  但我有充分的理由
Well, excuse me for living, but I've got a damn good reason.
我不管
I don't care what your reason is.
你不能就这么随心所欲地
You can't just waltz in and out of my precinct
进出我的分局
whenever you want.
我妈妈可是吓坏了  警监
Uh, my mother was traumatized, captain.
不管你喜不喜欢  我都得参与这件案子
I'm involved in this case, whether you like it or not.
好吧  但我会盯紧你的
Fine. But you're on a short leash.
有多紧我说了算
Oh, I'll decide how short my leash is.
刚跟罗宾的假释官通过电话
Just got off the phone with Robyn's parole officer.
看我发现了什么  罗宾的妈妈
Look who I found... Robyn's mama.
"妈妈"奥利维亚·图森特
Olivia "Mama" Toussaint.
是个卖派对毒品给富二代的中层毒贩
She's a mid-level dealer who sells party drugs to rich kids.
罗宾两年前被抓时就是她手下的一员
Robyn was part of her crew two years ago when she got busted.
罗宾被捕是因为什么
What was Robyn arrested for?
盗车重罪  疏忽致险
Uh, grand theft auto, reckless endangerment,
破坏私产
destruction of private property.
罗宾去一家长岛的乡村俱乐部
Robyn made a delivery to a country club
送货  但留下参加派对来着
On long island, decided to stay for the party.
她喝醉后  偷了辆车  撞进了房子里
She got wasted, stole a car, drove into a house...
损失高达50万美元
Half a million dollars' worth of damage.
去阿尔比恩监狱蹲了两年
Got her two years in Albion correctional, too.
那么罗宾现在获得假释  妈妈就去剧院
So, with Robyn out on parole, mama must have gone
想再把她招回麾下
to the theater to bring her back into the fold.
但罗宾不肯  还威胁要把妈妈供出去
But Robyn refused and threatened to rat mama out.
于是妈妈就永远封了罗宾的口
So mama silenced Robyn for good.
好吧  把她找来
All right, boys, bring her in.
好
All right.
告诉我  "妈妈"是个讽刺吗
Tell me... is the "Mama" meant to be ironic?
让未成年孩子替你贩毒可不像个妈妈
Not very motherly having underage kids run drugs for you.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
那罗宾·金呢
What about the name Robyn King?
记起来了吗
Does that ring a bell?
当然  怎么了
Sure. What of it?
她为你蹲了两年监狱
She did two years in prison for you.
你大概觉得你每月往她监狱
You probably thought the $40 a month you put
小卖部存的40美元足以收买她的忠诚
in her prison commissary account would keep her loyal.
但我猜事与愿违
But I'm thinking it didn't.
所以你才去了趟剧院
That's why you stopped by the theater
想摆老妈的谱  让她愧疚
to lay down a little - old-fashioned motherly guilt.
或者是想强迫她回到你手下
Or was it to strong-arm her back onto your crew?
我是去看她的  确保她一切都好
I went there to check on her, make sure she was okay.
我们有目击证人说你到的时候怒气冲冲
We got a witness that says you were angry when you showed up.
没办法  她伤了我的感情
What can I say? She hurt my feelings.
是啊  孩子啊
Yeah. Kids.
不打电话  不写信
They don't call, they don't write.
可不是
Tell me about it.
按理说  他们该知道感激
You think they'd show a little gratitude
而不是为了新家庭而甩掉你
instead of dumping you for a new family.
所以你就杀了她吗
Is that why you killed her?
因为她开始跟别人混了
'cause she started running with that other crew?
我没杀她  警探
I didn't kill her, detective.
我去了那儿  把想说的说了  我就走了
I went there, I said my piece, I left.
我能证明
And I can prove it.
这个新家庭
This new family...
不会是在西班牙哈莱姆吧
they wouldn't happen to live in Spanish Harlem, would they?
我怎么知道
Hell if I know.
罗宾说是在监狱里搭上了他们
Robyn said she hooked up with them in prison
而且他们有重大计划要执行
and that they had a big thing coming up.
审妈妈审得如何
How'd it go with mama?
她的不在场证明核实了
Oh, her, uh, alibi checks out.
她8:15就已经上了出租
She was in a cab by 8:15.
看来罗宾在跟新的团伙混了
And it looks as though Robyn was working with a new crew.
我早先真的很开心
I had a really great time earlier.
我也是
Me too.
我现在想吻你是不是很不对
Is it wrong that I want to kiss you right now?
不对到对
So wrong, it's right.
-真抱歉  -为什么
- I'm sorry. - For what?
你个混蛋
You're a jerk!
哥们  没事吧
H-hey, bro, you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
不  她好使劲啊
No. Ow! Man, she hits hard.
卡塞尔  显然你在这儿
Look, Castle, I-it's clearly not okay,
是个问题
you being here.
嗯  你还是回家吧
Yeah, you better go home.
我们有发现会打给你
We'll call you if we find anything.
你是对的
You're right.
泡泡  很舒缓
The bubbles... very soothing.
妈妈  你在干什么
Mother. What are you doing here?
你该在家休息的
You should be at home, resting.
得了  我怎么休得了
Please. How can I possibly rest?
还要抓杀人犯呢
There's a murderer to catch.
听我说  我得提醒你  我们发现证据
Listen, I-I have to warn you... we found evidence
表明罗宾可能回归了犯罪生活
that Robyn may have returned to a life of crime.
不会  那姑娘是个好人
Nonsense. That girl has a good heart.
我知道她在努力改变自己的生活
I know she was trying to turn her life around.
我们开工吧  我能帮什么忙
So let's get to work. What can I do to help?
好吧
All right.
我们知道罗宾每周两次去西班牙哈莱姆
We know that Robyn was meeting with her new crew
见她的新团伙
twice a week in Spanish Harlem.
我觉得她手机上的这些符号
And I think these symbols on her phone
跟下次会议有关系
have something to do with her next meeting.
那么问题在哪
So, what's the problem?
我不会符号表情语
I don't speak emoji.
第一个符号
I think that first symbol there...
那个按钮  显然是个钟
the buttony thing... is a clock, obviously.
而且指针在12点方向
Uh-huh, and the hands are on 12,
那么罗宾的团伙是中午见面
So Robyn's crew is meeting at noon.
不对  是午夜
Not noon... midnight.
这样我们还有一小时
So that gives us less than an hour
研究出含义  赶去市区
to figure this out and get uptown.
好吧  一只羊  一个耳朵
Okay, so we have - a sheep, an ear,
一个D  一只公牛
a "D," a bull,
一个包  沙滩球  和鱼竿上的鱼
a bag, a beach ball, and a fish on a pole.
表情符号可以代表其他东西
Emojis are symbolic for other things.
当然  问题是它代表的是什么
Clearly, but symbolic for what other things?
你会去哪儿钓鱼
Well, where would you go fishing?
水边
Water.
河边
By the river.
可这和羊有什么关系
What does that have to do with sheep?
表情符号大多是合成词
Well, emojis are often compound words,
所以"羊"加上"耳朵"
So "sheep" plus "ear"...
加上字母D可以是...
plus "D" could mean...
羊耳朵...牧羊人
Sheep eared. Shepherd.
-牧羊人  -没错
- Shepherd. - Exactly.
-那公牛呢  -固执吗
- And the bull? - Stubborn?
华尔街吗  但那不在西班牙哈莱姆区
Wall street? That's not in Spanish harlem.
公牛是金牛座的符号
Bull is the astrological sign for taurus.
确实  这有帮助吗
It is. Does that help us?
我们先做个标记
We'll put a pin in that.
接下去是包和球
Next are the bag and the ball.
那可不是普通的包
And not just any bag.
那是个购物袋
That is a shopping bag.
你当然是最熟悉购物袋的
An item with which you are intimately familiar.
连起来是  购物球
So, shopping ball?
不  广场  购物广场
No - -  mall. Shopping mall.
等等
Wait a minute.
午夜  河边
Midnight by the river
到谢泼德·托雷斯[金牛座]购物广场
At the Shepherd Taurus shopping mall?
干得漂亮  走吧
Well done. Let's go.
等等  我们不报警吗
Wait, wait. Shouldn't we call the cops?
对  那附近不安全
Yeah, that's a kind of dangerous neighborhood.
女士们  下层住宅都高档化了
Ladies, with all the gentrification going on,
河畔的地产怎么会不安全呢
there's no such thing as bad riverfront property.
好吧  可能是我错了
Okay. Maybe I was wrong.
当心脚下
Watch your step.
也许我们该给埃斯波和莱恩发个短信
Maybe we should be texting Espo and Ryan.
我已经打过电话了  他们在赶来
I already called them. They're on their way.
我都不知道该庆幸还是该伤心
I don't know whether to be happy or hurt
你这么不信任我
by your lack of faith in me.
好吧  我是该庆幸
Okay, I'm gonna go with happy.
-那是只老鼠吗  -老鼠没那么大
- Was that a rat? - That's too big to be a rat.
-"真棒"  -走吧
- Great. - Come on.
我受够了
All right, that's it.
爸  你看
Dad. Look.
*因为我不打算一个人来*
*Cause I'm not planning on the going solo*
*离开之前  叫醒我*
*Wake me up before you go go,*
*今晚带我起舞*
*Take me dancing tonight*
*我要声飞云霄*
*I'm gonna hit that hiiiiiiiigh yeah yeah yeah*
*你让我心跳不已*
*You put the boom-boom into my heart*
*当爱意袭来  你让我的灵魂飞升*
*You send my soul sky-high when the loving starts*
*脑海响起爵士*
Jitterbug into my brain*
*音乐不停  我脚下也起舞*
*It goes a-bang bang bang till my feet do the same*
*如果你有什么烦恼*
*If something's bugging you,*
*如果有什么不对劲  我的好朋友告诉了我*
*If something ain't right my best friend told me*
*你昨晚做了什么*
*What you did last night*
*你让我睡在我的窗上  我进入梦乡*
*You left me sleeping in my bed I was dreaming,*
*但其实我该跟你在一起的  这爵士乐*
*But I should have been with you instead, Jitterbug*
大家准备好开始即兴对唱了吗
Are you ready for the riff-off?!
音乐分类已经过时了
Category is blasts from the past!
*当你紧紧将我拥住*
*When you hold me in your arms so tight*
*我就知道  一切都好*
*You let me know, everything's all right*
*我迷上了一种感觉*
*I-I-I-I'm, I'm hooked on a feeling*
*我一心坚信*
*And I'm high on believing*
*你是爱上了...*
*That you're in love --*
*我们曾经的爱似乎*
*The love we share seems to*
*毫无前途*
*Go nowhere*
*我丧失了我的生活*
*And I've lost my life*
她带着和罗宾一样的手链
She has the same bracelet that Robyn had.
她们一定是在等罗宾出现
They must be waiting for Robyn to show up.
-*我要逃离你*  -来
- *Now I'll run from you* - Come on.
*我不在意你的爱*
*This tainted love you're givin'*
*我要你们...*
*I'll give you all...*
你们是在等罗宾吗
Are you looking for robyn?
你们是谁
Who are you?
她叫阿丽克西斯  我是理查德·卡塞尔
Uh, this is Alexis, and I'm richard castle.
我们是私家侦探
We're private investigators.
我们是来询问关于罗宾的事的
We're here to talk to you about robyn.
她出什么事了吗
Did something happen to her?
纽约警察  都不许动
NYPD! police! Nobody move!
纽约警察
NYPD!
卡塞尔
Castle.
有什么紧急情况
Where's the 911?
那是...
That was - -
这些是什么人
Who are all these people?
罗宾的新伙伴
Robyn's new family.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
罗宾是监狱里第一个和我讲话的人
Robyn was the first person to talk to me in prison.
她一直照顾着我
She always had my back.
你们队的女孩都是在监狱里认识的吗
Is prison where all the girls in your group met?
对  通过不倒退团体认识的
Yeah - -  through the N.B.P.
不倒退团体
Uh, no backsliding partnership.
是个公益艺术项目  防止我们再走歪路的
It's a nonprofit arts program that helps us stay straight.
我们都爱唱歌  是罗宾把我们组织起来
We all loved singing, but robyn was the one
成立了无伴奏演唱社团
who put together the a cappella group.
没有她就没有我们无罪团
Without her, there is no aca-cons.
你知道谁有可能杀了她吗
Do you have any idea who might have killed her?
艾格尼丝
Agnes.
她是我们的一员  直到三个月前
She was in the cons -  till about three weeks ago.
发生了什么
And then what happened?
我们都在排练  准备参加
We were auditioning for the A.A.C.,
全美无伴奏演唱大赛
the all American Acappella Competition.
我们本来胜利在望  不可能失败
We were crushing it. No way we could miss.
除非有人搞砸
Unless somebody screwed up.
艾格尼丝吗
Somebody like Agnes?
我们无罪团的成员  都是初犯
Look, the aca-cons, we're all one-time offenders.
我们都很努力想不再走歪路
We work really hard to stay clean.
但艾格尼丝是个惯犯
But agnes... she's a repeat offender,
她根本不想从良
and she's not interested in changing.
所以与其拿这样的大事冒险...
So rather than take a chance before your big break...
我们踢她出局了
We kicked her out.
我们都投了票  但是罗宾去告诉了她
We all voted, but Robyn was the one who told her.
艾格尼丝很气愤
Agnes was pissed...
说罗宾在她背后捅刀
accused Robyn of stabbing her in the back.
艾格尼丝·莫利纳  三次入狱
Agnes Molina...  three-time loser
前科累累  包括入室盗窃和伤人罪
with a long list of priors, including b&e and assault.
看来现在又要加上杀人了
Looks like we can add murder to that list.
我们比对了她的指纹
Yeah, we ran her prints
和剧院现场搜集到的指纹
against the ones we found at the theater.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
是匹配的
We got a match.
-那她现在在哪儿  -不知所踪
- And where is she now? - She's in the wind.
艾格尼丝昨天没向假释官报到
Agnes didn't check in with her parole officer yesterday.
警员搜过了她的公寓
Unis searched her apartment.
她似乎是打包离开了
Looks like our girl packed up and left.
肯定有人知道她藏在哪了
Well, someone's got to have a lead on where she's hiding.
我们也这么想
Yeah, that's what we figured.
所以我们叫来了不倒退团体的组织者
Yeah, so we asked the couple that runs the N.B.P.
斯科特和琳达·温伯格夫妇
to come in - -  Scott and Linda Weinberg.
好  我去和他们谈谈
Great. I'll talk to them.
你们去调查艾格尼丝  看能发现什么
You guys dig into Agnes' life, see what you can find.
我们创办这个组织时还都是
We started this organization when we were both
年轻律师  想要回馈社会
young lawyers looking to give back,
看到对这些女孩的巨大帮助之后
and the difference we made for these girls was so profound
我们决定倾力帮助她们
that we dedicated our lives to helping them.
你们了解艾格尼丝·莫利纳吗
So, how well do you know Agnes Molina?
怎么了  她是疑犯吗
Why? Is she a suspect?
是的
Uh, yeah. She is.
警监  艾格尼丝确实做了很多坏事
Captain, Agnes certainly did some bad things in her life,
但她人不错  不可能杀人
but she's a sweet kid, not a killer.
你知道她现在在哪里吗
Do you have any idea where she is now?
不知道
No.
上次被捕之后她父母就把她赶出去了
I mean, her parents shut her out after her last arrest.
那朋友呢
And what about friends?
在监狱里有
In jail, yes.
但是外面就
But on the outside...
只有组里的姑娘们了
Just the girls in the group.
肯定还有其他朋友
There's got to be somebody else.
如果艾格尼丝有麻烦她会找谁
I-if Agnes was in trouble, who would she go to?
她有个前男友
There was an ex-boyfriend.
他到监狱看过她一次
He visited her in prison once.
前男友的名字叫德克斯特·格莱姆斯
Ex-boyfriend's name is Dexter Grimes.
他是个有前科的下岗焊接工
He's an unemployed welder and ex-con.
听着像是个金龟婿
Sounds like a real catch.
另外  先生们  就像我说的
And, gentlemen, as I told you,
贝克特对我跟着来没有意见
Beckett is fine with me riding along.
对  她是没意见
Oh, yeah, she's fine with it.
我记得她的原话是
I believe her exact words were,
可以  说不定运气好塞尔吃子弹了呢
"Sure. Maybe we'll get lucky and Castle will get shot."
真的吗  过分
Really? Ouch.
你做了什么
What'd you do?
什么都没做
Nothing.
你被扇耳光了  卡塞尔  你绝对干了什么
You got slapped, Castle. You definitely did something.
还是干了谁
Or someone.
你出轨了
You cheated?
什么  没有
What?! No!
卡塞尔  别跟我们撒谎
Castle, don't you lie to us.
贝克特是我们的家人
Beckett's our family.
你对不起她  就是对不起我们
You cheat on her, you cheat on us.
那个女的叫什么
What's her name?
伙计们  我说的是实话
Guys, I'm telling you the truth.
抓到我的肉了
That's my skin!
她  叫  什  么
What...is... her...name?
斯维特拉娜
Svetlana?
-斯维特拉娜  -斯维特拉娜
- Svetlana? - Svetlana!
怎么  她是俄国内衣模特之类的吗
What, is she some kind of Russian underwear model?
是吧
Uh, yeah?
你们在搞什么鬼
What the hell are you doing?
纽约警局
NYPD.
我们进来了
We're coming in.
你就是德克斯特·格莱姆斯
So, Dexter Grimes,
你最近一次见艾格尼丝·莫利纳是什么时候
When was the last time you saw Agnes Molina?
艾格尼丝吗
Agnes?
好几年没见了  她被抓之前的事了
Haven't seen her in years -- before she got busted.
少蒙人  德克斯
Nice try, Dex.
我们知道你去监狱看过她
We know that you visited her in prison.
她现在在逃
And now she's on the run.
你这么好  我们想她肯定跑到你这来了
You're such a catch, we figured she came running to you.
我告诉你  我跟她已经结束了
I'm telling you -- me and her are done.
我不知道她在哪里
I got no idea where she is.
真的吗
Is that right?
那这个唇印是
So, then, this lipstick is from...
我妈的
My mom.
那么
I suppose...
这是你妈妈的内衣
This is your mom's bra?
对
Yep.
不太像
Fat chance.
事实上  德克斯特  我认为艾格尼丝藏在
Matter of fact, Dexter, I believe Agnes is hiding...
这里
...right here.
差点就骗到我了
Almost had me.
不幸的是我知道
Too bad I know...
她在这下面
She's under here!
天呐  谁把衣服堆在
Man, who piles clothes under...
有点紧张了吧  德克斯
Getting a little nervous, Dex?
我是不是越来越
Am I getting...
热[接近]了
warmer?!
不是吧
Seriously?
在那后面
Behind the...
我刚才就在那边
I was right there.
就在这里
Yes.
这应该是你的
I believe this is yours.
我们知道你去过剧院  艾格尼丝
We know you were at the theater, Agnes.
我们发现了你的指纹
We found your prints.
你们以为我为什么要跑
Why do you think I ran?
我一听说罗宾死了
The second I heard Robyn was dead,
我就知道你们会赖到我头上
I knew you'd pin it on me.
所以你是说  你没有杀罗宾
So you're saying - that you didn't kill Robyn?
因为我们听说她把你踢出组合
'cause we heard you were pissed
你很生气
when she kicked you out of the group.
我的确很生气
Damn straight I was mad.
但是我没去计较
But I walked it off,
就像我的监狱辅导员教我的那样
just like my prisoner counselors taught me.
昨天是罗宾打给我
Robyn called me yesterday,
叫我昨晚十点去剧院见她
asked me to meet her at the theater last night at 10:00.
为什么
Why?
她说她需要一个保镖
She said she needed a bodyguard
需要人保护她
and somebody to keep her safe.
保镖  艾格尼丝  你好歹编得像一点
A bodyguard? Agnes, come on. You can do better than that.
是真的  她要给我五百块
It's true. She offered me 500 bucks.
有钱永远能使鬼推磨
Money trumps feelings every time.
好吧  那她要防着谁
Okay. Who did she need protection from?
我不知道
I don't know.
她只说是一个无伴奏比赛里的人
All she said, it was somebody from the a cappella competition.
她说等我到了再细说
She was gonna tell me more when I got to the theater,
但是我晚到了几个小时  她不在我就走了
but I was a couple hours late, and she wasn't there, so I left.
看来她当时其实就在那里吧
But I guess she was there, huh?
但已经死了
Dead.
罗宾被杀的时候  有人看到
We got witnesses that put Agnes in a diner across town
艾格尼丝在城市另一端一家餐厅里
during the time Robyn was killed.
也就是说我们的凶手估计是
Which means our killer is probably
比赛里的人
someone inside the competition.
伙计们  谁给卡塞尔报了信
Guys, who tipped Castle off?
不是我们  尤其他还...
Not us. Not after, uh...
还怎么
After what?
卡塞尔跟我们说了
Castle told us about...
斯维特拉娜的事
Svetlana.
他说了吗
He did?
他跟你们说了
He -- he...told you about...
斯维特拉娜  对的
Svetlana -- yeah.
我们很遗憾  贝克特
We're so sorry, Beckett.
你想的话我们可以把他扔下楼梯
If you want, we should throw him down a flight of stairs?
不用了  我会...
N-no, I'll -- I'll -- I'll take --
嗯  我自己会处理的
Yeah, - I-I-I'll handle this myself.
-不如你们进去找人问问话吧  -好吧
- Why don't you guys go in and interview some people? - Okay.
谢谢你打给我  我尽快赶来了
Thanks for the call. I came as soon as I --
怎么了
What?
斯维特拉娜
Svetlana?
嗯  我之前就想告诉你
Yeah. I, uh, I was gonna tell you about that earlier,
但我想我应该当面告诉你比较好  所以
and I thought it would be better if I told you in person, so...
-所以  -所以  小伙子们
- So...? - So, uh, the boys --
他们起了疑心  说我出轨
they got suspicious and accused me of cheating.
我慌了  所以现在他们以为
I panicked, and now they think
我在和一个叫斯维特拉娜的俄罗斯模特约会
I'm dating a Russian model named Svetlana.
你就不能起个好听点的名字吗
And you couldn't think of a better name?
对吧  我也觉得
Right?! I know!
那是我唯一能想到的名字  我也不知道为什么
It was the only name I could come up with. I don't know why.
不过说回来  她是个模特
But still, she's a -- she's a model.
是个非常非常火辣的模特
She's a really, really hot model.
算你说对了
Damn straight she is.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你好  我是贝克特警监
Hi. I'm Captain Beckett.
我们需要和负责人谈谈
We need to speak with whoever's in charge.
好的  我就是
Yes, that would be me.
我是拉森博士  全美无伴奏演唱大赛地区赛主管
I'm Dr. Larson, director of the A.A.C Regionals.
裁判长  全权负责这次比赛
Head judge. I oversee all aspects of this competition.
那你一定认识罗宾·金
Oh, so then you would have known Robyn King.
不好说  她和我不是一路人  如果你懂我意思
Vaguely. She wasn't my kind of people, if you know what I mean.
你似乎对她的死讯并不吃惊
You don't seem very shaken up about her death.
当然这很可怕  但我并不能说感到吃惊
Well, it's horrible, of course, but I can't say I'm surprised.
她和她的朋友  并不是全美无伴奏演唱大赛的料
She and her friends - are not exactly A.C.A material.
因为他们有前科  你的意思是
Because they're ex-cons, you mean?
全美无伴奏演唱大赛是个备受尊重的正规机构
The A.A.C. Is a highly respected and civilized institution.
我告诉全国委员会
I told the National Committee
让她们这种人参与进来是个错误
it was a mistake - to have their kind involved.
但是他们听了吗  没有
But did they listen? No.
拉森博士  昨晚九点到十一点之间你在哪
Dr. Larson, where were you last night between 9:00 and 11:00?
就在这
Right here.
让演出顺利进行需要24小时都费心
Getting the show off the ground is a 24-hour job.
如果你们还有其他需要  请联系我的助手特洛伊
Now, if you need anything else, talk to my assistant, Troy.
请不要打扰任何演出者  谢谢
Please do not upset any of my performers. Thank you.
这家伙渣到天上了
This guy for real?
很不幸 是的
Unfortunately, yeah.
你现在想怎么做  警监
So, what do you want to do now, Captain?
我们去和其他参赛者谈谈
Let's talk to the other contestants.
莱恩跟我来  埃斯波  你和卡塞尔
Ryan, you're with me. Espo, it's you and Castle.
击掌
High five.
击
High --
打扰一下  你们是旅男团吗
Excuse me. Are you the Travel Boys?
*绝无仅有最牛掰组合  你们是谁*
*The one and only badass crew. Who the hell are yo-o-o-u?*
纽约警局  我们需要问你们几个问题
NYPD. We need to ask you a few questions.
*我得拒绝  兄弟  兄弟*
*Gotta say no no bro bro*
*我们在为演出热身*
*We're warming up for the sho-o-o-w*
真是烦人
Okay. That's annoying.
你想怎么做
What do you want to do?
交给我
I got this.
*你想唱*
*You wanna siiiiing?*
*我们来唱唱罗宾·金但你们最好坦白*
*Let's sing about Robyn King but you best be straight,*
*因为你一定不想尝试我手铐的滋味*
*'cause, baby, you'll hate to feel the steel of my handcuffs.*
*我今晚就让你锒铛入狱*
*I'll take you to the jail tonight.*
这是罗宾的化妆间
This was Robyn's dressing room.
你上次见到她是什么时候
When was the last time you saw her?
昨天  彩排之后
Yesterday, right after rehearsal.
应该是五点三十左右
Must have been about 5:30.
她从这里冲出去  几乎把我撞倒
She stormed out of here -- practically ran me over.
她很沮丧吗
Was she upset?
非常  但是我不知道为什么
Very. But I don't know why.
-她去哪了  -不知道
- Where'd she go? - No idea.
但我听说她大约半小时后离开的剧院
But I heard that she left the theater about a half-hour later.
舞台监督助理
The assistant stage manager
看到她在前门上了一辆出租车
saw her getting in a cab out front.
我得和他谈谈
Okay, well, I need to talk to him,
另外我们需要一份
and we also need a copy
罗宾昨天彩排安排的复印件
of Robyn's rehearsal schedule from yesterday.
没问题
Sure.
谢了
Thanks.
我们开始吧
Here we go.
-贝克特  -怎么了
- Beckett. - Yeah?
你还好吗
You doing okay?
还好
Yeah.
我听到斯维特拉娜的时候  很难过
You know, I was crushed when I heard about...Svetlana.
是吗
You were?
我觉得这样再好不过
You know, I think it's for the best.
-是吗  -是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
事实上  我也在和别人交往
As a matter of fact, I'm dating someone else, too.
一名医生  利文斯顿医生
A, uh, a Dr... Livingstone.
-莱恩  你听到了吗  -听到了
- Ryan? Do you hear that? - Yeah.
我的错  我全喷在自己身上了
Oh. I got it. I spit all over myself.
-正中我的眼睛  -我喷到你了也  抱歉
- Got me right in my eye. - I got you, too? Sorry.
只是一时忘情
This made me -- caught up in the moment.
卡塞尔  是你吗
Castle? Is that you?
贝克特
Beckett?
你们在做什么
What are you doing?
我们只是在
We're just in --
你们在做什么
What -- what are you doing?
我们在罗宾的化妆间里
We're in the middle of Robyn's dressing room.
她昨晚五点三十从这里跑出去
She ran out of here at 5:30 last night.
很显然  她当时非常沮丧
Apparently, she was very upset.
也许是因为她在这里听到的什么事
Maybe over something she heard in here?
你们其中有谁昨晚五点三十在这个房间吗
Were any of you boys - in this room 5:30 last night?
-没有  -不在
- Nope. - No.
我不在
Not me.
有人逃跑
Got a runner!
让开  让开  让开
Move, move, move, move! Move! Move!
不许动
Don't move.
好
Sure.
这都是个天大的误会
This is all a big misunderstanding.
你真的想玩这种游戏吗
Do you seriously want to play that game?
我们无所谓  双手抱头
Yeah, fine by us. Put your hands on your head.
等等  我们能做个交易吗
W-wait. Can't we work something out?
当然  如果你告诉我们真相
Yeah -- if you tell us the truth.
罗宾听到了你们化妆间里的一些事
Now, Robyn overheard something from your dressing room.
是不是
Didn't she?
我知道我们组合比不过无罪团  好吗
I knew that my group couldn't beat the Aca-cons, okay?
比不过她们那正能量的
Not with their feel-good,
"无伴奏演唱团《女子监狱》版"的幕后故事
"Orange is the new singing sensation" backstory.
所以我  我就
So I... I sort of...
你是想操纵比赛结果吗
Did you try to fix the competition?
是的
Yeah.
-我贿赂了拉森博士  -主裁判吗
- I bribed Dr. Larson. - The head judge?
是他自己一直说个不停
He was the one who was going on and on about
说无罪团就不该来参加比赛
How the aca-cons shouldn't even be in the competition,
他们达不到全美无伴奏演唱大赛的标准如何如何
How they weren't up to the standard of the A.A.C.
他接受你的贿赂了吗
And did he accept your bribe?
接受了  但是罗宾无意听到了
Yeah, but Robyn overheard us,
我们的谈话  闯了进来
and she burst in.
她威胁说要向全国委员会举报
She threatened to tell the national committee.
我看这就是谋杀动机
That sounds like motive for murder to me.
对我来说并不是
Not for me.
拉森博士说他能搞定  就和罗宾一起走了
Dr. Larson said he'd handle it, and then he left with Robyn.
我只知道这些
That's all I know.
你们最好能解释清楚为什么把我拖到这里来
You better have one heck of a good reason to drag me down here.
我警告你们  我认识不少人
I'm warning you -- I know people.
哦  我们也是
Oh. So do we.
比如亨特
People like Hunter.
知道吗  他交代说你受贿
You know, he told us that you took a bribe
要把无罪团清出比赛
to get the aca-cons out of the competition.
这是奇耻大谎
That is an outrageous lie.
那个叫亨特的家伙  我敢说他才是凶手
Now, that Hunter fellow -- I bet he's the killer.
是的  他这是利用你们
Yes, and he is trying to manipulate you. Mm-hmm.
说不定他说的对呢
Maybe he's right.
是啊  说不定
Yeah, maybe.
等等  不可能是亨特
No. Wait. Couldn't be Hunter.
想起来了吗  他有不在场证明
Remember -- he has an alibi.
哦  对啊
Oh, yeah.
对啊  真该死
That's right. Damn it.
我们觉得该回到原点怀疑你了  博士
I guess we're back to you, doc.
所以你做了什么  安排一次会面
So, what did you do -- arrange a meeting
是不是罗宾不肯配合
And when Robyn wouldn't cooperate with you,
你就杀了她
is that when you killed her?
我没必要杀她
There was no need to kill her.
我们达成协议了
We'd worked out a deal.
罗宾已经准备告发我了
Look, Robyn was all set to report me,
但是突然发生了奇怪的事情
But then something... peculiar happened.
奇怪
Peculiar?
是的  我们离开了亨特的化妆室  登台表演
Yes, we left Hunter's dressing room, and onstage,
大家排练到一半
The crew was in the middle of a tech rehearsal.
屏幕上播出了无罪团的介绍视频
The aca-con introduction video came up on the monitors.
罗宾看了之后
Robyn watched it.
突然之间
And then, suddenly, just like that...
就改变了主意
She changed her mind.
你是说
S-so you're saying
罗宾看了个什么视频
that Robyn changed her mind about ratting you out
就决定不告发你了
because of what she saw in some video?
正如我所说  很奇怪
Like I said, it was peculiar.
但是罗宾保证只要我不接受贿赂
But Robyn promised not to say anything,
她就什么都不说
so long as I rejected the bribe
所以我给她拷了一份介绍录像
And gave her a copy - of that introduction video.
造化弄人  我进了监狱之后
Ironically, I didn't find my love for singing
才发觉自己对歌唱的热爱
until I went to prison.
18岁的罗宾已经有两年贩毒史
At 18, Robyn had already been running drugs for two years.
她的生活一片狼藉
Her life was a mess.
有一次给乡村俱乐部送货之后
And after making a delivery to a country-club party,
她偷车出了车祸
She stole and crashed a car.
实际上  我烂醉如泥
Truth is, I was so wasted,
完全不记得当时发生了什么
I don't even remember what happened.
罗宾被困在了着火的车里
Robyn was trapped in the burning car.
然后上天给她派来了一位英雄
But then, the universe sent her a hero.
我开车回家路上  突然间
I was driving home, and then --
天啊  有车祸
Oh, my god -- car crash.
我把罗宾从车里拉出来  拖到安全地带
I pulled Robyn out, I dragged her to safety,
然后我只能用她的围巾
And then I had to tourniquet her leg with her scarf
给她止血
to stop all the bleeding.
就像从灰烬中涅槃的凤凰
And like a phoenix rising from the ashes,
罗宾走出悲剧开始了全新的生活
Robyn emerged from this tragedy and started a new life.
那场车祸是我生命中最好的事情
That crash was the best thing that ever happened to me,
因为入狱  我成功戒毒
Because in prison, I got clean,
加入了不倒退团体  并且
Hooked up with the N.B.P., and...
这挽救了我的人生
And it saved my life.
女士们先生们  这就是无罪团
Ladies and gentlemen, the aca-cons.
-为什么罗宾对此感兴趣  -注意了
- Why would Robyn be so interested in this? - Hey.
我找到了罗宾从拉森博士那里
I managed to track down that cab that robyn jumped into
拿到视频后打的那辆出租车
After she got the dvd from Dr. Larson.
她去哪儿了
Where'd she go?
上东区的市政厅
Townhouse on the upper east side.
看看住在那里的是谁
And look who lives there.
这绝对不可能是巧合
That cannot be a coincidence.
这么说
So...
你是不是在罗宾被害当晚见过她
...you saw Robyn the night that she was murdered, huh?
是的
Yeah.
回头想想有点诡异
It's kind of eerie, - if you think about it, huh?
是啊  我是说  她去找你做什么
Yeah. I mean, why would she visit?
她是想亲自登门拜谢
Well, she wanted to thank me personally.
你看  我救罗宾的时候她昏迷不醒
You see, Robyn was unconscious when I saved her.
等她康复之后
Then after she recovered,
就直接进了监狱
She went straight to prison,
所以我们一直没机会正式见面
So we never actually properly met.
波西  你是个真英雄
Ah. Well, Percy, you are a real hero.
过奖了  你们才是英雄
No, you're the heroes.
我只是在正确的时间出现在正确的地点罢了
I was just in the right place at the right time.
别这么谦虚
Mnh-mnh. No, don't be so modest.
如果不是你用围巾给罗宾的腿包扎
If you didn't make a tourniquet out of that scarf,
她可能就失血过多而死了
Robyn could have bled out and died.
说到那条围巾  是哪来的
Speaking of that scarf, where did it come from?
是罗宾戴着的
Um... Robyn was wearing it.
是吗
She was?
那就有意思了
Oh. That's funny.
因为我们联系了
Because we reached out
接收罗宾的那家医院
to the hospital where robyn was taken,
根据收诊表上的内容
And on her intake form,
存在一点时装界的悖论
There's a bit of a-a fashion discrepancy.
你看  罗宾全身行头加起来也就50块钱
Y-you see, Robyn's entire outfit was worth about $50.
你用的那条围巾  可是爱马仕
But the scarf that you used, it was an Hermes scarf,
价值两千元左右
And that was worth about 2 grand.
所以我好奇的是
So what I'm wondering is...
你为什么说谎
Why are you lying to me?
好吧
Okay.
你能保密吗
Can you keep a secret?
不能
No.
但是那你也得告诉我
But you're gonna tell me anyway.
救罗宾命的人不是我
I didn't save Robyn's life.
我赶到现场的时候
By the time I got there,
她已经安全了  但是浑身冰冷昏迷不醒
She was already safe and passed out cold,
腿上已经用围巾打好了绷带
And the scarf tourniquet was on her leg.
你为什么说谎
Why would you lie about that?
为了做英雄
To be a hero.
你知道这件事发生后我推特涨了多少粉吗
Do you know how many Twitter followers I got after that?
这么说  罗宾知道了事情的真相
So, uh, Robyn figured out what really happened,
所以她才会去你家
and that's why she came to your house?
她想知道真相  我就告诉她了
She wanted the truth, so I told her.
有人把她从车里拉了出来
Somebody else pulled her from the car.
他们肯定是...走掉了
Then they must have... run off.
一切肯定都跟这有关
That's what all this must have been about.
罗宾在查探她被捕的事情
Robyn was digging into her old arrest.
是啊  她的发现导致自己被害
Yeah, and whatever she found got her killed.
视频里  罗宾说她嗨爆了
In that video, - Robyn said she was so high,
她什么都不记得
she didn't remember anything,
那她怎么知道是她偷的车
So how does she know that she's the one who stole that car?
因为波西告诉她  她是一个人
Because Percy said she was alone.
但他在说谎  有人在那
But he was lying. Someone else was there.
如果当时是那个人在开车呢
And what if that someone was the one driving the car?
你想想  逃离车祸现场的原因是
Think about it -- a reason to leave the scene of an accident
你是肇事者
is that - you were the one responsible.
有人撞了车  把罗宾拉出来
So someone else crashed the car, pulled Robyn out,
跑掉  让罗宾顶罪
ran off, leaving Robyn to take the fall.
但在那之前  那人用围巾包扎了罗宾的腿
But not before bandaging Robyn's leg with their own scarf.
就是说如果罗宾发现了围巾的主人
So if Robyn found out who that scarf belonged to
然后跑去跟那人对质
and then confronted them --
那人很可能就是凶手
There's a good chance that person's our killer.
伙计们  我跟乡村俱乐部通了电话
Hey, guys, I talked to the country club,
我发现了开派对的人是谁
and I think I found the woman who threw that party.
她叫克洛伊·贾维斯
Her name is Chloe Jarvis,
而她  是长岛的帕丽斯·希尔顿
and apparently, she is, like, the Paris Hhilton of Long Island.
听你的口气  好像这挺牛逼似的
You say that like it's a good thing.
但派对是好多年前了
Yeah, but that party was years ago.
我们怎么查出是谁戴了围巾呢
How are we gonna find out who was wearing the scarf?
照片
Photos.
因为克洛伊有个疯狂照片集账号
Because Chloe has a snappamatic account.
聪明
Smart thinking.
希望派对的照片还在上面
Hopefully, the photos of that party are still up.
该死  克洛伊的账号是私密的
Damn. Chloe's account is private.
我们没有足够的合理根据  申请搜查令
And we don't have enough probable cause yet to justify a warrant.
准确地说  是纽约警局需要合理根据
Excuse me -- the NYPD may need probable cause.
理查德·卡塞尔侦探社嘛  就....
Richard Castle Investigations, however...
不行  卡塞尔
No, Castle.
你不能
You cannot...
以纽约警局的名义  黑进克洛伊的账号
hack Chloe's account on behalf of the NYPD.
我们绝对禁止你那样做
We absolutely forbid you.
说实话  没了我  你们怎么破案
Honestly, how did you guys ever solve murders without me?
经常破案啊
All the time.
卡塞尔去哪了
Hey, where's Castle going?
那个...
S--
你不想知道的
You don't want to know.
贝克特  你不需要他
'cause, Beckett, y-you don't need him.
听着  我就是想说
And -- and look, just so you know,
分手了  我俩归你
You get us in the breakup, okay?
没错
Oh, yeah. Damn straight.
总之呢...
Anyway...
我在查阅苏福克郡警局
Um, I was looking over Robyn's arrest reports
关于罗宾的逮捕报告
from the Suffolk County PD.
没啥料  但是
It's pretty thin, but apparently,
他们保存室的证据箱不见了
the evidence box in their property room is missing,
也就是说要么他们本职工作干得很糟
which means either they're practicing really shoddy police work...
要么有人帮助神秘车主陷害罗宾
Or somebody helped our mystery driver to frame Robyn.
没错
Exactly.
当时执行逮捕的警官叫丹·奥格雷迪
The arresting officer's name is Dan O'Grady.
他刚刚退休  搬到了曼哈顿
He just retired from the job and moved to Manhattan.
-警察退休金住曼哈顿  哪那么容易  -是啊
- Kind of cushy - for a cop on a pension, huh? - It is.
带他来问话
All right, bring him in.
我不知道该说什么  警监
I don't know what to tell you, Captain.
证据肯定是被错放了
The evidence... must have been misplaced.
电话问问接待警员
Call the desk sergeant --
不  证据不见了
No, evidence is missing --
尤其是那条被医院
Specifically, the Hermes scarf
送过去的爱马仕围巾
that was sent over by the hospital.
你把围巾搞到哪去了
So what did you do with it?
你以为自己是谁  丫头
Who do you think you are, lady?
我来这纯粹是给你面子
I came here as a courtesy,
你却指责我渎职
and you're gonna accuse me of misconduct?
我没有指责你任何事
I'm not accusing you of anything.
你的银行账户说明了一切
Your own bank account is.
罗宾认罪后一周
A week - after Robyn took a plea deal,
你五天存了五笔钱  每次都是9900美元
You made five deposits -- $9,900 each -- over five days.
我不必听你胡扯
I don't have to listen to this.
一旦你离开这间办公室
The moment you leave this office,
我将给内务部打电话
I will be calling internal affairs.
你想让我跟他们说什么
What do you want me to tell them?
你协助侦破罗宾的谋杀案
That you were helpful in solving Robyn's homicide
还是你妨碍司法公正
or that you obstructed justice?
完全取决于你
It's your call.
听着
Look.
你...
You, um...
你得明白
You got to understand.
我当时还有四个月就要被强制退休
I was four months away from mandatory retirement.
我几近破产
My bank account was a joke.
我走投无路
I was desperate.
罗宾被捕后那天
The day after Robyn was arrested,
我接到了一个女人的电话
I got a phone call from some woman.
-谁  -我没问名字
- From who? - I didn't get a name.
她说如果我能把案子的证据
She said she'd give me 50 Gs
全部交给她  可以给我五万美金
If I gave her all the evidence from the case,
尤其是...
Especially, uh...
那条围巾
That scarf.
进入了克洛伊的账号
I am in...Chloe's account.
阿丽克西斯  搜索
Now, Alexis, do a search
克洛伊在乡村俱乐部高尔夫球场的派对
for Chloe's golf course party at the country club.
那是罗宾
Oh, there's Robyn!
她真是个可爱的姑娘
She was such a lovely young woman.
她没戴那条围巾
And she's not wearing the scarf.
我没看到别人戴
I don't see anyone that is.
等下  那里
Wait -- there.
是那条围巾
There's the scarf.
改变罗宾生活的那个女人
So, the woman who changed Robyn's life
同时也是毁掉她生活的人
is also the one who took it.
琳达  你是怎么认识罗宾的
Linda, how did you know Robyn?
通过不倒退团体
Through N.B.P.
她是我们第一位囚犯参与者
She was one of our first prison participants.
事实上  你们早在那之前就认识
Uh, actually, you met long before that.
只是罗宾醉得不省人事  不记得了
Except Robyn was too wasted to remember.
我想我们都不记得了
I guess we both didn't remember.
那是条漂亮的围巾
That's a wonderful scarf.
很昂贵
Very expensive.
你用它来救罗宾的命  真是太慷慨了
It was very generous of you to use it to save Robyn's life.
但那样做也是理所应当
But, then again, it's the least you could do,
鉴于撞车的人是你
considering you're the one who crashed the car.
我没有
No, I didn't.
你知道吗  我记起来了
You know what? - it's coming back to me now.
在派对上  我把围巾给了罗宾
I-I gave Robyn that scarf at the party --
作为礼物
As a gift.
听着  琳达  我知道  你害怕
Look, Linda, I get it -- you were scared.
如果你被发现  你会进监狱
If found out, you would be sent to prison,
被法学院开除
kicked out of law school.
你的未来将灰飞烟灭
Your entire future would go up in flames.
于是你逃走  留下罗宾顶罪
So you ran, and you let Robyn take the fall.
你证明不了
You can't prove any of this.
不要这么确定
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
我追查到了打给奥格雷迪警官的电话
I traced the call made to Officer O'grady.
是你的手机打出的
It was from your phone.
我跟你的开户银行通过话
I also spoke with your bank.
他们找到了你贿赂他
They found the $50,000 withdrawal
的五万美元取款
you used to pay him off.
我不知道我在想什么
I-I don't know what I was thinking.
我慌了
I panicked.
罗宾入狱后  我...
And after Robyn went to jail, I just...
我很愧疚
I felt so guilty.
所以你才成立不倒退团体吗
Is that why you started N.B.P.?
我以为那样会帮到罗宾
I thought maybe I could help Robyn,
弥补过失
Somehow make a difference.
结果她发现了真相  跟你对质
Except she found out the truth, confronted you,
所以你杀害了她
and that's why you killed her.
我没杀罗宾
I didn't kill Robyn.
我都不知道她知道了真相
I-I didn't even know she found out the truth.
琳达  坦白吧
Look, Linda, it's time to come clean.
我坦白了
I just did.
我撞了车  逃离现场
I crashed the car, fled the scene,
但我没杀罗宾
but I didn't kill Robyn.
谋杀发生时  我在费城出差
I was in Philadelphia on business at the time of the murder.
还有谁知道车祸
Who else knew about the crash?
我想跟我的律师谈谈
I'd like to speak to my lawyer now.
所有选手  最后确认  还是10分钟开场
All groups, final checks. 10 minutes until curtain.
理查德  感谢你让我来
Oh, Richard, thank you for letting me be here.
当然  老妈  你应该在这里
Of course, mother. You should be here.
琳达  是我
Linda. Hey. It's me.
演出要开始了  你在哪儿
The show's about to start. Where are you?
温伯格先生  你可以挂掉电话了
Mr. Weinberg, you can hang up the phone.
你妻子被关在12分局
Your wife's being held at the 12th precint.
为什么  怎么回事
Why? What the hell's going on here?
我们知道是你杀了罗宾
We know you killed Robyn.
这太扯了
Excuse me, but that's absurd.
我们排查了你的公寓
We canvassed around your apartment.
我们在垃圾桶里找到了一件你的T恤
We found one of your shirts in a dumpster
上面有罗宾的血
with Robyn's blood on it.
当她得知你妻子是车祸的真正肇事者
When she realized your wife was behind the car accident,
罗宾来找她了  不是吗
Robyn came looking for her, didn't she?
她很生气
She was pissed.
琳达出城了
And Linda was out of town,
所以我告诉她琳达会在她上班的地方跟她碰面
So I told Robyn I'd have Linda meet her at her job.
但你不过想让她落单  以便杀了她
But you just wanted to get her alone so you could kill her
让妻子的秘密永不见天日
and bury your wife's secret forever.
不
No.
我想让她明白  如果真相大白
I wanted to make her understand that if the truth came out,
会毁掉一切  我们的心血
It would ruin everything -- all we had worked for.
你们的心血
All that you girls had worked for.
所以你就杀了她
And that's why you killed her?
不不  那是个意外
No. No, no, it was an accident.
她说我是骗子  伪君子  我就...
She was calling me a liar and a hypocrite, and I just...
我推了她  突然  她撞到了头
I pushed her, and suddenly, she hit her head off --
斯科特·温伯格  你因谋杀
Scott Weinberg, you're under arrest
罗宾·金而被捕
for the murder of robyn king.
最后彩排
Final rehearsal.
无罪团  你们是下一个
Aca-cons, you're up next.
你们是罗宾的朋友吗
Oh, are you -- are you Robyn's girls?
听着  我认识她
Oh, listen, I'm an acquaintance of hers.
我叫玛莎·罗杰斯
My name is Martha Rogers.
我只有一个特长  表演
I only have one real specialty -- performance.
如果我能帮到你们
But if I can assist you in any way at all...
-当然  -那样太棒了  -好的
- Absolutely. - That would be great. - Yes? Okay.
亲爱的  帮我拿一下
Darling, could you hold that for me?
你要施展魅力了  母亲
You gonna work your magic, mother?
那当然  孩子
You bet your best-selling novels I am, kiddo.
听我说
All right, now I want you to listen to me.
我知道这很艰难
I know how hard this is. All right?
但你们做得到
But you can do this.
你们可以从悲伤中走出  为了罗宾赢下比赛
You can rise above your sorrow and win this for robyn.
好吗
Yes?
-好的  -上场吧
- Yes. - Let's go.
上台  深呼吸
I want you to go up there, take a deep breath...
伙计们  感谢你们让我参与这案子
Guys, I really appreciate you letting me help out on this one.
你知道的
Well, you know...
我们愿为玛莎做任何事
We'd do anything for Martha.
是啊  我们还是喜欢她的
Yeah. We still like her.
你们是说因为我和贝克特分居了
W-- are you saying that because Beckett and I are separated
咱们就不能做朋友了吗
that we can't be friends?
听着
Look...
最开始  我们觉得这是暂时的
At first, we thought - it was just a temporary thing,
但现在你们开始约会其他人
but...now we know - you're dating other people.
这提醒了我
Oh! That reminds me.
我得去准备与斯维特拉娜的约会了
Got to get ready for my hot date with Svetlana.
写报告写得开心哦
Have fun with that paperwork.
什么
What?
如果你需要发泄  我们陪你
If you need to vent, we're here for you.
是啊  如果需要我们可以整晚彻谈
Yeah. We can -- we can talk all night if you need to.
啊  你们知道吗
Yeah. Uh, you know what?
谢了  伙计们  但
Um, thanks, guys, but I've got
我要去跟性感医生约会了
A really hot date with that doctor.
-利文斯顿  -是的
- Livingstone? - yeah.
只有我这样想吗
Is it just me, or is this just...
他们这样太不靠谱了
wrong -- all kind of wrong.
谁啊
Who is it?
斯维特拉娜  性感的俄罗斯情人
Svetlana -- your sexy russian lover.
更正  我的性感俄罗斯情人
Correction -- my sexy russian lover
恰好还是个模特
who happens to be a model.
戴上
Get the...
利文斯顿医生吗
Dr. Livingstone, I presume?
找不到我的遮阳帽  所以呢...
Couldn't find my pith helmet, so...
人人美剧「在线播放」
震撼上线
欢迎前往苹果商店
及各大安卓市场下载人人美剧客户端
来
Come.